

MATHEUS FELIPE TRINCA

ANALISTA DE SISTEMAS

Tengo más de 5 años de experiencia y aprendizaje en Desarrollo híbrido con React, React Native y NodeJS. Adoptando buenas prácticas y siempre enfocándome en crear codigos limpios y reutilizables, que puedan ser fácilmente interpretados y tengan un fácil mantenimiento.

CONTACTO

Lugar de Residencia: San Isidro, Buenos Aires.

Whatsapp: 11 27453966

Tel Móvil: 11 27453966

E-Mail:

matheusfelipetrinca@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/matheus-trinca

CERTIFICACIONES

React Front to Back

The Complete React Native y Hooks NodeJS API with Express and MongoDB Ruby on Rails SQL y NoSQL

Python de básico a avanzado Java Orientacion a Objectos

Red de Computadores

Protocolo TCP/IP

Routing e Switching

Conceptos de Firewall

Redes Wireless

Seguridad de Redes Wireless

IDIOMAS

Inglés: Intemédio Espanhol: Intermédio Portugués: Nativo

FORMACIÓN ACADÉMICA

ANÁLISIS Y DESAROLLO DE SOFTWARE

FATEC, Garça - SP | 2018

SEGURIDAD DEL TRABAJO

ETEC, Marília - SP| 2010

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

ANALISTA DE SOFTWARE

LINX | ENERO 2023 - ACTUAL

- Desarollo Front End con React Native, ReactJS y Ruby on Rails
- Desarollo Back End con Ruby on Rails
- Material UI, Redux, Context API
- NextJS
- Innovaciones y corrección de errores de la aplicación

ANALISTA DE SOFTWARE

NEEMO| ENERO 2019 - ENERO 2023

- Desarollo en React Native y ReactJS
- Material UI, Redux, Context API
- NextJS
- Actualización y mantenimiento de la aplicación

ANALISTA DE ECOMMERCE Y DESARROLLADOR

ALUÁ FIESTAS | ENERO 2016 - DICIEMBRE 2018

- Análisis de mercado, categorizacion de precios, publicidad y marketing de productos.
- Sistema ERP (OnClick), plataforma Tray e integración con Mercado Libre
- Como Desarrollador trabajé en un proyecto de ranking y mejora Google, contextualizando tags HTML, optimizando SEO y mejoras de layout.



MATHEUS FELIPE TRINCA

ANALISTA DE SISTEMAS

Tenho mais de 5 anos de experiência e aprendizado em Desenvolvimento híbrido com React, React Native e NodeJS. Adoção boas práticas e sempre focando na criação de produtos limpos e reutilizável, que pode ser facilmente interpretado e ter uma fácil manutenção.

CONTATO

Lugar de Residência: San Isidro, Buenos Aires.

Telefone:

11 27453966

F-Mail:

matheusfelipetrinca@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/matheus-trinca

Github:

https://github.com/MatheusTrinca

CERTIFICAÇÕES

React Front to Back

The Complete React Native y Hooks NodeJS API with Express and MongoDB Ruby on Rails

SOL e NoSOL

Python de básico ao avançado

Java Orientação a Objetos

Rede de Computadores

Protocolo TCP/IP

Routing e Switching

Conceitos de Firewall

Redes Wireless

Segurança de Redes Wireless

IDIOMAS

Inglês: Intermediário Espanhol: Intermediário Português: Nativo

FORMAÇÃO ACADÊMICA

ANÁLISE E DESENVOLVIMENTO DE SOFTWARE

FATEC, Garça - SP | 2018

SEGURANÇA DO TRABALHO

ETEC, Marília - SP| 2010

HISTÓRICO PROFISSIONAL

ANALISTA DE SOFTWARE

LINX | JANEIRO 2023 - ATUAL

- Desenvolvimento Front End com React Native, ReactJS e Ruby on Rails
- Desenvolvimento Back End con Ruby on Rails
- Material UI, Redux, Context API
- NextJS
- Inovações e correção de bugs

ANALISTA DE SOFTWARE

NEEMO| JANEIRO 2019 - JANEIRO 2023

- Desenvolvimento em React Native e ReactJS
- Material UI, Redux, Context API
- NextJS
- Atualização e manutenção de aplicações

ANALISTA DE ECOMMERCE E DESENVOLVEDOR

ALUÁ FESTAS | JANEIRO 2016 - DEZEMBRO 2018

- Análise de mercado, categorização de preços, publicidade e marketing de produtos.
- Sistema ERP, plataforma Tray e integração com Mercado Livre.
- Como Desenvolvedor atuei em um projeto de ranqueamento e melhoria do Google, contextualizando tags HTML, otimizando SEO e melhorias de layout.



TRINCA

DEVELOPER

I have more than 4 years of experience and learning in hybrid development with React, React Native and NodeJS. Adopting good practices and always focusing on creating clean and reusable, that can be easily interpreted and easily maintenance.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Location:

San Isidro, Buenos Aires.

Phone:

+54 9 11 27453966

F-Mail·

matheusfelipetrinca@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/matheus-trinca

Github:

https://github.com/MatheusTrinca

CERTIFICATIONS

React Front to Back

The Complete React Native and Hooks NodeJS API with Express and MongoDB Ruby on Rails

SOL and NoSOL

Python basic to advanced

Java OOP

Networking

Protocol TCP/IP

Routing and Switching

Firewall Concepts

Wireless Network

Wireless Network Safety

LANGUAGES

Inglês: Intermediate Espanhol: Intermediate Português: Native

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT

FATEC, Garça - SP | 2018

WORKPLACE SAFETY

ETEC, Marília - SP | 2010

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DEVELOPER

LINX | JANUARY 2023 - ACTUAL

- Front End development with React Native, ReactJS and Ruby on Rails
- Back End developement with Ruby on Rails
- Material UI, Redux, Context API
- NextJS
- Innovation and bug fixing

DEVELOPER

NEEMO| JANUARY 2019 - JANUARY 2023

- Front end development with React Native and ReactJS
- Material UI, Redux, Context API
- NextJS
- Application maintenence

ECOMMERCE ANALYST AND DEVELOPER

ALUÁ FESTAS | JANUARY 2016 - JANUARY 2018

- Market analysis, price categorization, advertising and product marketing.
- ERP system, Tray platform and integration with Mercado Livre.
- As a Developer, I worked on a Google ranking and improvement project, contextualizing HTML tags, optimizing SEO and layout improvements.